Idol group Taru pulls and introduces cute and spilling information
The whole entertainment program is called "Pull Pull Pull Information Bureau"!
Yes, that's right, continuing from last time
We are here at Masquerade Idol at the Country Spares Hall.
Masquerade Idol at Country Spare Hall!
Yay!
This time, more than 25 idol groups will be performing.
We, the new members, are trying to improve our interviewing skills.
We've been interviewing a lot of idols.
How was it last time?
It was my first interview.
It's really nerve-wracking.
But you're too good a person not to be.
It might be rude to say I've been watching them for a while.
I mean, I've been watching idols since I was in school, so...
So it was that easy?
This is tough.
I know, right?
It was really tough, but...
But he was so kind.
He let us watch the show.
After the show, they took pictures of us.
He was so kind.
They told me to do my best.
They are nice people.
They've been here for years.
They are really nice.
I'm going to do another interview, so let's do our best.
Let's do our best.
Let's go!
Yay!
Ooh!
Yes, our first guest is Amefranci.
Hello.
Let's at least make an error here.
Let's make it happen with you
I'm a girl mine Tell me now I don't need any more meaningless words
Greetings. We are...
I'm Ameflash
Yes, I'm Chisato Yuzuki
Yes, I'm Kojima Shu
Yes, I'm Suzuki Mayaka
Yes, I'm Aira.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Yes, I'm looking forward to working with you.
This is my first interview. I'm a little nervous.
Great.
Why?
Because it's nice.
I remember when I did my first interview with you.
She was a-haing for about five minutes.
We're one of a kind, aren't we?
Pleased to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
First of all, please tell us what makes your group Ameflash.
We try different kinds of music.
We have a core.
We have a core, but we also try to create fun songs, cute songs, cool songs...
Cute songs, cool songs...
We are a group that is confident in our performance.
We are confident in our performance.
Thank you for letting us perform live.
Thank you very much.
It's really cool.
I'm glad.
With that wallop.
I've been working with Mr. Yuzuki for a while now.
I've been working with Yuzuki a lot.
What? Yuzuki is really...
He's got a huge gap.
He's dissing me, Wallop.
In a good way.
In a really good way.
The rap...
Hey.
I'll take care of you. Good timing.
I don't think I've ever seen him like that.
It's like you're in charge of MCing.
Thank you very much.
We don't know how to MC at all.
I was wondering if you could give us some tips.
Tips?
I'm already in control here.
Or so I think.
Or so you think.
It's okay to bite.
It's like nothing happened.
Putting it all together
Thank you so much!
The reason why Kobikazu originally became the MCAnd that's why Kobikazu became MC originally.
He's the one who doesn't talk the most.
He didn't talk at all.
So he was forced to speak.
That's why he became MC.
That's what we're doing now.
I see.
Also, Aira's TikTok is going around.
It's going around?
I got this one too.
Oh, wow.
It's like once in a thousand years.
Actually, it's not once in a thousand years.
I've seen it about 10 times.
You've done it many times?
I did it in a row. I was practicing.
I was practicing.
What's the point of mixing them?
I don't want to tell you.
We also felt like we were getting buzz in places we didn't expect.
I looked at my footage, and I was having so much fun.
I'm having a lot of fun.
There's a lot going on in my life.
All of it.
It's a great reference for me.
I also try my best to be a good cameraman for my clients.
And they're good at it.
I think it's more about the client's skill than ours.
With their help.
Don't put half of it in the magazine at all.
I don't know if I've told them that.
Even if I told them, they wouldn't print it.
It's pretty strict.
I think it's tough.
If you set your own judging criteria to be strict.
I'm sure it would get a lot of buzz.
Maybe.
I don't know.
And I...
We're going to be high school classmates.
Oh, wow.
Thank you.
I'm really nervous about this job.
It's the first time I've ever been nervous.
And I'm not an idol at the time.
I'm so nervous.
Really?
Really.
That's all I have to say.
That's it?
Stop it.
Let me try.
Was it a nice, quiet, mature section in there?
It was a quiet, mature section.
It wasn't like a school or anything.
It's more like a demure highbrow kind of image.
That's the image.
For us, it's unbelievable.
What kind of character is she?
Oh, no.
Let's say from now on...
He's always on time and always late.
LOL.
That's not it.
He's got this image of being on time.
She might be the sweetest.
I'm the oldest, but maybe the sweetest.
He often asks me if I'm doing anything weird with my makeup.
She's cute.
She's like a beloved character.
Loved character.
You can say that a lot.
People say that a lot.
They give me tons of compliments.
I'd like to say it with you.
Okay, so...
Takumi, do you have any last announcements for Anemura-san?
Yes, we are celebrating the release of our coffee on May 16th.
We are currently holding a Lily second drawing!
The next release will be on June 11 and June 24.
If you would like to see them, please come and visit us at Jinbei Seinen Mingei.
I would be very happy if you could come and visit us.
Thank you very much.
And on July 9, there will be a one-ban live bion festival at Shinjuku Lady!
Yay!
Tickets are now on sale.
It's going to be a really big event with guests and stuff, so please come and join us!
Some of the guests are young men and women
There will be finks at all!There are no finks at all.
So note, so we have both some people club youth.
I hope you can come to both.
Thank you very much.
Yes, so the second one was Milacutan. Thank you very much.
Okay, the interview is over.
My heart has already skipped a beat today.
My heart's already pounding.
No heart, right?
No heart, really.
But let's keep working on it, and let's get better and better at interviewing new members, too.
Let's do that.
What is it?
I'm so tired I can't think straight.
I'll do my best, so please keep watching.
Please keep watching.
Yes, I'm in the middle of something serious, but I have an announcement from NATURL this time.
Vine June 24 at Kangaspere Hall,
NATURL's 9th anniversary one-man live concert will be held at Kangaspere Hall.
Yay!
This is an important one-man live for the first year since the new organization was formed.
Please come and play with us.
LUNA, what would you like people to see?
This will be our first solo live since our debut in the new year,
I would like you to come and see how much we have grown.
Please come and see how much we have grown.
Please come.
See you at Kangaspere Hall on June 24th.
I will be waiting for you.